[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "Our preliminary surveys did not differentiate between different types of questions, so we were unable to ____ this issue.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ put forward in this paper depends in no degree upon the completeness of our knowledge of the former condition of the organic world.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A ____ for other cultures is inherent in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Truman managed to win a narrow ____ with 49.5 percent of the popular vote.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Waldorf Education method considers the teacher's ____ development to be a significant factor in the educational process of the children.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A frequent error in editing is to fix a word or ____ at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students must ____ that at least one of the three courses they take to satisfy the general and school cores is a Humanities course.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Lack of ____ revenue often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is virtually impossible to ____ which infants in the latter group will not survive without support.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "predict", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has failed in its primary task, ____ to reduce unemployment.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The results on the tests are ____ to expectations.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most people have a ____ notion of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If we ____ just a little more, we will see that random is hardly the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Because there was the threat of losing funding if they failed to participate, there was a strong ____ to do so.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She has been an important exponent, nationally and internationally, of the ____ that artists have a critical role to play in democratic societies.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Another common meaning of ____ is the date on something has to be done, as in Don't forget. Your project is ____ tomorrow.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Different newspapers will often have a different ____ of the same event - especially newspapers from different parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the government's decision to invade Iraq.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Smartboard is an excellent ____ for teaching language.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The boss was right to ____ that his workers would return to work once it was clear that they would otherwise lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Mild pain and inflammation can often ____ an otherwise rewarding day of skiing.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Even with support, because of his health and limits on the hours he could work, he was unable to ____ the duties of the typical teaching job.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, thus is unable to ____ insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The district cannot ____ the accuracy of the information or the appropriateness of any material that a student finds.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The first principle of this school is that all nationalities and cultures are equally important, even if some are more represented than others ____ the body of students.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new ____ should help to reduce the number of problems resulting from adjustment to semester length.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A major ____ in his success was his willingness to work very hard.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you don't ____ search results within that time frame or if this an urgent request, please contact the reference desk.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The patient was not at all happy with the ____ of treatment she received while in hospital.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In order to self-correct your writing, you need to get an ____ diagnosis of your problems.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ was asked to compile a report listing the reasons in favour of invading Iraq.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not in employers' interest to get rid of cheap illegal immigrants - only to ____ them of any rights.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To prevent this from happening, it is very helpful for patients to avoid talking unless ____ necessary for three days following surgery.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government needs to use a more ____ approach to persuading people to eat less and keep fit.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Shortage of research space remains a ____ constraint for future development.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This illustrates the variety of ____ choices that a criminal would make in the decision to commit a crime.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In most countries the ____ for the place where you can get information is the letter 'i'.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teachers are not ____ in favour of the school's plan to introduce flexible working times.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ to believe that the quality of my thinking has not diminished; I simply have chosen a different format to express my ideas.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The American colonists did not ____ a real newspaper of their own for another century.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government official wrote to ____ that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is not in employers' interest to get rid of cheap illegal immigrants - only to ____ them of any rights.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Do not omit the ____ after an abbreviation such as in. (for inch), which could be confused with the word in.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Even with support, because of his health and limits on the hours he could work, he was unable to ____ the duties of the typical teaching job.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You need to try and ____ your thoughts a little more clearly. This does not make much sense to me.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unfortunately, heroines of this sort are not ____ in oral tales, and do not exist at all in any of the Grimm tales.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Beethoven was not an ideal parent and enormous ____ developed between the two, contributing to his son's attempted suicide in 1826.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The evidence is overwhelming that prediction markets provide a more ____ prediction than polls.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Although there are a number of ____ strategies for trying to retain employees, money appears to be the most powerful retention tool with regard to top performers.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Dartmouth has received a number of complaints, specifically ____ their poor fact-checking.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The evidence is overwhelming that prediction markets provide a more ____ prediction than polls.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the incident damaged the atmosphere for the upcoming talks on ____ matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The teacher's threat to give the student a detention had an ____ impact on his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The bulk of the urban districts, particularly in the Northern states, were totally ____ to this development.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was not until about 500 years ago that scientists and doctors began to examine the ____ of the human body.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school has made the difficult decision to ____ the wearing of religious symbols in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a comprehensive final exam.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Science should be about objective facts, not ____ opinions.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The best proof of this is that the institutional unity provided for by the Treaty of Maastricht did not ____ for even one year after the treaty was ratified.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Her consistent efforts throughout the school year are certain to ____ excellent results in her final examinations.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The current program review process is not very ____ because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most serious problems that ____ the new government.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government is finding it difficult to break the ____ of poverty and poor school performance.", "Opt_1": "assignment", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of native-English speakers and non-native-English speakers at the school is about 40% : 60%.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This could substantially change the nature of the Internet we have come to know, to the ____ of both the consumers and the providers of information.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In this next task you need to ____ with the person sitting next to you.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "cooperate", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is no doubt about it - the seafloor of Baku harbor is ____ dead.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The German government should have realized that it would ____ matters by allowing the different German states to have their own regulations about smoking in public buildings.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "exchange", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In this ____ poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's sphere is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school will ____ a new floor in the sport hall over the summer vacation.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She has not been making much ____ in the last few weeks. I think the counselor should talk to her and find out if anything is wrong.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Curiously absent from the report is any ____ of the type of action that the State would have taken against the diverse sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This ____ provides a quick and extremely simple way to collect written feedback on student learning.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government failed to keep its promises and ____ was voted out of power at the next election.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Great Britain, Canada, and the United States do not intend to reveal the secret until ____ have been found to control the bomb.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The prime ____ of a strong academic vocabulary is that it helps you to read school textbooks more efficiently.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The best footballers can ____ many thousands of pounds every day.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This document explains how to ____ password protection from your Web site.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The new government has not yet proved itself ____ of making the right decisions in its foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school's decision to raise the tuition fees will have a serious ____ on the number of students who plan to attend.", "Opt_1": "concern", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Scientists ____ that most children born today in First World countries will see their 75th birthday.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many schools in poorer parts of the world do not have ____ books and computers to give their students a good education.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I ____ we are going to have a test on this. - You are right!", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "create", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you currently do not possess the ____ to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "John continue to ____ that he gave me his homework, but I'm certain he didn't.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Individual academies ____ the curriculum in the manner that best fits local facilities and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has decided to ____ financial aid to the African country until the civil war is over.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teenage alcohol ____ is an enormous problem in some UK cities.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The first principle of this school is that all nationalities and cultures are equally important, even if some are more represented than others ____ the body of students.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "\"We hope to ____ the historic value of these buildings and encourage serious parties to step", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "By running these ads, the newspaper is sending the message that it considers this a ____ product to sell.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She has gained ____ good grades since she has started attending school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people have claimed that the ____ reason for the invasion of Iraq was to gain control of the oil fields.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She was raised by a family that did not ____ the significance of racial differences and the importance of developing a positive racial identity.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school chose not to ____ news of the teacher's accident.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She was in ____ with her parents at home and this was having a negative effect on her schoolwork.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not ____ a successor and therefore gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Depression can ____ from sense of tiredness, low motivation and concentration, to severe difficulties with managing one's daily life.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "An employee or University student who wishes the matter to ____ a formal investigation and review should contact the EEO Officer.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a ____ in electrical energy leading to the construction of power stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Both children and adults can be encouraged to be ____ learners, but their needs as language learners are often different.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government plans to offer ____ parenting classes for young, unemployed couples.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After ____ criticism the government has decided to restore language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is important to ____ that the information noted on the sign-off form is correct and that all necessary signatures have been obtained.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To remain eligible for financial aid, recipients are required to show ____ progress toward a degree according to the guidelines listed below.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She has massive problems with her spelling. There was ____ a word she got right in the dictation.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Our focus is to motivate each student to achieve their full potential as they ____ for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When the models incorporate the effects of pollution, they predict that rainfall will ____ even more in the next few decades.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This report draws on lessons learned from previous ____ deployments to consider strategies to protect the health of troops in future deployments.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Not many people will change their habits or lifestyle ____ because a government minister tells them it's a good idea.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is thinking of passing a law that will require all house owners to ____ their oil heating system for one that runs on gas.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "exchange", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You must remember to ____ all the images and other HTML documents you have created and referenced in your \"Public/html\" directory.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She has learned from her mother's experience, however, and does not ____ the error her mother made.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We should seriously pursue the idea of the internet elections, which are a totally ____ option.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We held that the entry was illegal because police failed to ____ their purpose before using the crowbar to pry the door open.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company has the ____ to dismiss employees without giving a reason during the first 6 months of their employment.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids ____ sound better than air.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you want to travel at half-price on the trains and buses in Frankfurt, you need a ____ identity card with the school stamp.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Until recently there have been few sources of information about the morphological and syntactic ____ of the Kam language.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Not all scientists agree with the ____ that the earth is getting warmer because of human pollution.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "School need to ____ their curricula on the needs of the students who attend them.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Harvard is probably the most famous education ____ in the USA.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must ____ a plan to remove greenhouse gases from the atmosphere without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The business manager could not explain the ____ in the company's finances, and was asked to resign.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She needed to ____ enough money to be able to afford London's sky-high prices.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We can conclude that China is unlikely to put significant ____ on Sudan, and that Sudan could and would easily resist such ____.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "No ____ can have much effect on the environment, but people working together can make a big difference.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This famous ____ will assure her place in the history of sport.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They ____ the food directly to needy families and individuals.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "form", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is not the correct procedure to use when comparing two ____ databases.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To include an ____ on your website, you will need to insert the ____ into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no ____ upon her behaviour at home. She is allowed to do whatever she wants.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and occasionally requires travel away from the normal ____ station.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government ____ wrote to confirm that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The global ____ agreements have failed to include meaningful, enforceable labour or environmental standards.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Honesty is not an attribute that most people ____ with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "With her departure we have decided to ____ teaching Spanish this fall as we await the committee report.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government is planning to make a ____ tomorrow morning on its discussions the doctors' union.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These questions are meant to help you research the background information you will need to ____ some of the water quality issues in NYC.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The common, misinformed man did not ____ that fleas infected black rats, which in turn bit humans.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An orange pencil is not a ____ tool to do your homework with.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The loose and often unclear ____ of the organizational responsibilities enabled energetic managers to network.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The President will ____ on TV this evening to talk about the riots in the capital city.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "FLO plays the key ____ as an agent for ethically sensitive consumers.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You can ____ of old batteries in the container outside the cafeteria.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Aycock stated that he had looked over the horse before the purchase and did not ____ any marks indicating that the horse had been cut.", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is a ____ chance to visit South Africa, and at the same time help build a school in the desert.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The study of how computers are similar to human brains is called ____ intelligence or AI.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some of the key personal resources that you will draw from include your ____ academic background, teaching style, life experience, and technical experience.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is concerned about the current high ____ of unemployment.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When you ____ an electrician to do a job in your house, you hope they will be competent at their job.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A battle to save life has ____ been waged at the Kwangtze Hospital in Shanghai. This battle is not yet over, but it has already caused a great sensation.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The head teacher could not ____ parents that there would be no increase in school fees.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ability to communicate accurately and effectively is a ____ component of the curriculum.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The equator is an ____ line that divides the earth into a northern and southern hemisphere.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I am no ____ in animal behavior, but anyone with even a slight knowledge of the field must be impressed with their complex forms of social behavior.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Because of their mobile lifestyle, they did not ____ many objects.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This line on the playground is the ____ to where you are allowed to go as a grade 7 student.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Doctors have ____ a connection between cannabis use and mental illness. This is especially a danger for people who have started taking drugs at an early age.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Audio software can help students to record their spoken words describing an ____ concept or how to perform a computation.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She was able to ____ the Smartboard screen controls so that the presentation was visible to everyone.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The new manager needs time to ____ her own style of leadership.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Hershey Corporation, however, already had a ____ to provide chocolate for the troops.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The most ____ risk factor in predicting whether a person will commit a violent crime in the future is whether the person has previous offenses.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He questioned the security coordination that enabled the terrorists to ____ all their preparatory work. The authorities had failed to surround the school for three days.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The police ____ give details of whom they have arrested until they know that the person will be charged with a crime.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Unfortunately, heroines of this sort are not numerous in oral tales, and do not ____ at all in any of the Grimm tales.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Certain items are not available at this time since the originals have been put into storage for the ____ of the construction.", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your vocabulary test scores are good but you take twice as long to learn the words as the other students. You need to use a more ____ method.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We have a ____ policy of no drugs in our school. You will be expelled if you are caught with them in the building.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "But when planned and deliberate policy forces the price of oil down without good commercial reasons, then that ____ another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "although"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The student said that his dog had eaten his homework. The teacher did not believe him but could not ____ what he said.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You should write this again to ____ all the irrelevant details.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You must try to achieve a ____ between work and play. At the moment it's too much play!", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The proposal is unlikely to ____ the tension between them.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a reasonable ____ for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The bulk of the ____ money that has been allocated to Afghanistan has been wasted.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will therefore attempt to ____ contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We all have to ____ differences of opinion in the political world and, in order to do that, we have to understand that there are real reasons for these differences.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on ____ of another, the former steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "For some people the ____ characteristics of a website are more important than its content.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ timing left the committee with only one working week to review the applications.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Participants donate a small amount of blood or saliva, which will be used as a ____ to blood from children with genetic diseases.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Part of the job of an ESL teacher in an international school is to ____ the need to make work comprehensible to non-native speakers.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "impose", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We have had no chance to examine changes of this sort systematically, but simply ____ them as examples of processes that we expect to be completed.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government is unpopular and is expected to fare badly in the ____ election.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Giving up the course was a ____ thing to do. He had no chance of passing it.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ prediction is that there will be no more oil by the end of the century.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "On the rare ____ when Crockett looks upon Indians with anything less than pure hatred, his observations continue to feed upon common stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I blame the linguists, for not insisting that anyone who claims to be an educated person needs ____ competence in describing and analyzing the sound, form and meaning of human language.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If we accept your request to amend the information, we will make ____ efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Before this century there was little ____ between them; indeed, they did not think of themselves as two distinct kinds of people.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has ____ published reports about farming in the UK and illegal drug-taking. The latter has created far more interest in the media.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This ____ provides an overview of several aspects of Egyptian culture.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most simply, the strength of a ____ is measured by determining how much energy is required to break the ____.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The purpose of this study is to ____ the stereotype that men are better in mathematics than women.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When a ____ minimum has been found using limits, the limits should then be removed if possible, in order to perform or re-perform the error.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "satisfactory", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ every significant detail about each of your customers.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The recent conference about green energy failed to ____ the interest of the British public.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The instructor is expected to ____ his or her grading policy at the beginning of the course.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The word give is substituted for the word ____ to express more clearly the intent of the section.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "encourage", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ workforce is opposed to the managers' plans to relocate the factory.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Both Initial and Wokingham now dispute the ____ for the cost of food and say it is lower.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We need one more teacher to ____ the cafeteria at lunch times.", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Errors in grammar and vocabulary may, but do not always, ____ with comprehensibility.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Political Bureau will work to ensure the ____ progress of the reform of the administrative system.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has invested little money in the health system. The quality of hospital care is sure to ____ more and more.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the ____ to take if you decide to use email as an official means of communication.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is important to note that the speed at which refracted light travels is dependent upon the density of the ____ it is traveling through.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Even with support, because of his health and limits on the hours he could work, he was unable to fulfill the duties of the ____ teaching job.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is not difficult to speculate on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our ____ to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has taken the ____ decision to consult the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A foreigner who wants to become a ____ of the USA cannot have a criminal record.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The two teams are ____ equal. It's difficult to predict who is going to win.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We will continue to see new immigrants coming to our city, and we will need to ____ their access into the medical care system.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Because of their ____ lifestyle, they did not accumulate many objects.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In fact, most of the errors discussed on this ____ are common in the writing of privileged middle-class Americans.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Your supervisor has been provided with the above information and should be able to ____ any questions you may have.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An abundance of research documents the biased and harsh treatment that Black defendants have received at the hands of ____ White jurors.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Very few companies can ____ cars of the quality of German makes such as BMW or Mercedes.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Study suggests macroscopic bilaterian animals did not ____ until 555 million years ago.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It will help to ____ the nuclear powers from developing more advanced and more dangerous weapons.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to ____ a variety of materials to complete this class.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This famous ____ will assure her place in the history of sport.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For financial reasons the government had to cut the ____ to help prisoners on their release from jail.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "surplus", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is often necessary to associate a ____ set of \"metadata\" with each data point in order to make that datum useful.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "No matter how good the lawyer's intuition and ____ to express himself or herself, the lawyer will not succeed unless he or she can analyze logically.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government should pay ____ attention to reducing unemployment among young people.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many people think that terrorism is the greatest problem affecting ____ today.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As life spans increase, the fraction of life spent in retirement will ____ unless we delay our exit from paid work.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In the Spring semester, CIS faculty plans to ____ three new courses in high demand.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There was also no apparent record of an attempt to measure the ____ between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The rules of the school ____ that you must leave your mobile phone in your locker and not bring it to class.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some historians still hesitate to ____ the incidents of 1915 as 'genocide ', choosing to use words like 'massacre ' or 'atrocities ' to describe the events instead.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unemployment rates are currently quite stable. There have been no ____ rises or falls in the last two years.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The principle behind this policy is that the rights of the individuals should be respected; subjects must ____ to participation in research.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The world's largest film ____ is in Hollywood, Los Angeles.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These calculations are ____ to perform and are executed rapidly compared to Monte Carlo.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I believe that people often ____ the hardships the parents experience if their child has a learning disability.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of the Urselbach river is high in the Taunus hills behind the school.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has increased ____ spending by 50% in the last two years.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Perhaps the most ____ example of an arthropod joint, indeed one of the most complex skeletal structures known, is the wing hinge of insects.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Why do people still ____ in living near volcanoes?", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We will not be able to distribute additional copies of the ____ until the printers strike is ended.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Despite the fact that there was a stream on the land, he could not ____ of the property at any price.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We still don't know if this is really the correct mechanism to ____ the imbalance between matter and antimatter that we observe.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more time to your studies and a little less time to your sports.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Theatre is not the correct ____ for such a performance, since it is a matter of the virtual as well as the actual.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please do not ____ me. I know what I said is correct.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Looking up all the ____ words in an important passage should be considered a background check for all literary analysis.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "German Liberals had tried and failed to ____ Germany during the Revolution of 1848.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government should do more to ____ immigrants who do not speak English.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most serious objection raised against the survey questions the use of self-report scales to ____ prejudice.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we are to contemplate actions designed to reverse the pattern of ____ difficulties in Viet Nam we ought to lay the groundwork.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "credible", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "believable"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A ____ example of ambiguity is the sentence: \"I do not like visiting aunts.\"", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly ____ hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The cost will not ____ anyone from participating in the program.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Prices have risen by ____ 4% over the last 10 years.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I don't believe that the government's plan to imprison more criminals is the best ____ for the problem of rising crime.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "However, no one ____ will be the sole reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Any student who is at least 13 years old on September 30 is ____ to enter the mathematics competition.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You need to include more detail. Your report has lots of general statements but very few ____ facts.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more time to your studies and a little less time to your sports.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government is thinking of passing a law that will require all house owners to ____ their oil heating system for one that runs on gas.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please ____ Einstein to your list of famous scientists.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government plans to examine the ____ data carefully before making an announcement.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school cafeteria has made the ____ decision not to offer hamburgers, hot dogs and French fries to the younger students .", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The difficulties that ____ from time to time in the business can be solved by good management.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "arise", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students successfully completing a family history major should ____ a significant range of skills and abilities in research and critical thinking.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a ____ approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many buildings ____ during earthquakes and kill the people inside.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ was unclear. It had been hand-drawn and then copied using weak ink.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many Western businesses are finding it difficult to ____ with Asian companies which pay their workers far less money.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As each hydrogen only has one electron to share in the formation of chemical bonds, it is impossible to ____ more than two hydrogen atoms to each other.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The protests failed to ____ Castro's arrival.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The entire ____ of Iraqi military and civil society collapsed so completely as the war ended, leaving a vast problem for American troops to handle.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but prior language study is not a ____ for selection.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has changed its ____ to nuclear power now that the cost of oil has been so high for the past few years.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government needs to decide on a ____ response to the continuing violent demonstrations.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Unless we reverse the trend, the consequence will be a sustained contraction in the number and quality of ____ scientists and research faculty.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some parents do not ____ how difficult it is to provide an education that will meet the needs of all students.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The B grade had come to ____ work that was barely acceptable.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please remember to ____ any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other damage to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a diverse global ____ will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government minister expressed ____ at her thoughtless comment about 'lazy incompetent teachers'.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I experienced her as a very ____ teacher who had empathy for her students.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The intelligence service is finding it very difficult to ____ which young men are likely to become terrorists and which are not.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Studies show that parents greatly ____ the development of their child in all areas.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Global warming will ____ cause big changes in California's coastal waters.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company's target for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this ____ by 40%.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many people oppose the ban on smoking in public places, but the ____ are in favour of it.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Illegal drugs are grouped into one or other ____ according to how dangerous they are considered.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Due to the severe shortage of highly trained nursing staff, Hopkins was unable to ____ a full team of qualified personnel.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "How people ____ to music is subjective. What sounds good to one person may sound terrible to another.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A ____ task in the English classroom is to classify the parts of speech into nouns, adjectives, verbs, etc.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Individual academies apply the curriculum in the ____ that best fits local facilities and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee recently announced his ____ to retire at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to focus not only on the skills and knowledge related to the high stakes tests but also the skills and knowledge to perform more ____ tasks.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We also want to speak openly about the question of whether the German radio should ____ so-called jazz music.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase ____ of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to align its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company does a minor amount of business in the USA; the ____ of its trade is in Europe.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are ____ laws that govern the trade in rainforest wood.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Once the conference is over the government will turn its ____ to the problems of urban crime.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Intelligence is just one ____ in being a successful student. You also have to show initiative and perseverance.", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The incoming president has made a ____ promise to reduce tax in the next period of government.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Department Coordinator, elected by peers, has the same one vote as the others and has no ____ over her peers.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ to the school grounds is the stream. You must not cross it.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The past 20 years have seen a ____ increase in our understanding of the biology of cancer.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The business has decided to ____ a large reorganization in the attempt to increase profits.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Studies show that parents ____ influence the development of their child in all areas.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Their acquaintance, therefore, it may be presumed, did not ____ till towards the end of this year 1754.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "commence", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to start", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He also was able to assist in identifying outstanding science curriculum ____ for the teachers in the district to review.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Men and women of all ages ____ from a moderate amount of daily physical activity (for example: 30 minutes of brisk walking or 15 minutes of jogging).", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students successfully completing a family history major should demonstrate a significant ____ of skills and abilities in research and critical thinking.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Because there was the threat of losing funding if they failed to participate, there was a strong ____ to do so.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As life spans increase, the fraction of life spent in retirement will rise unless we ____ our exit from paid work.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Those who had seen the march in Weimar at the 1926 party rally knew that National Socialism's march to ____ could not be halted.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The opening of the new sports block was the biggest ____ in the school's history.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental justice are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when ____ involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Therefore, if a farm has efficiency problems, simply expanding the operation may just ____ the problems.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Doctors are advising older patients to have an injection as a ____ against influenza this winter.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not ____ any tester who is cheating, but will complete the Testing Incident Report and submit to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He said that any art teacher who did not ____ students to ten thousand years of art was \"criminal.\"", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Specifically, you ____ that you were not provided with academic adjustments and auxiliary aids, and were not provided access to other services and programs at the College.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is very little ____ of the poor and middle class as our corrupt judges have developed a system called lawyer denial.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She has ____ problems with her spelling, but the content of her writing is actually very good.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to discuss topics early on with the instructor, especially in the case of an ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Since the U.S. flu vaccine ____ was cut in half early this month, shots are scarce, lines long and some people are certain to miss out.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government said that it had no ____ to give the reasons for its decision.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Carla Santos, a professor of leisure studies, says our perception of another culture is likely shaped by accounts of travel writers, who ____ to perpetuate cultural stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to ____ its responsibility to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually ____ exceptional performance remain out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Sports events such as the World Cup or the Olympic Games often ____ in an enormous firework display.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The conclusion did not distort the truth of the ____ even though the student distorted some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He claimed that Arab countries could not ____ Palestinians.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally rigid bodies ____ multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Since the human body is not an ____ that can be disposed of at will, the results of research should be made available to the whole scientific community.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You can ____ your risk of getting a cold in the winter if you avoid others who already have one!", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The name of this website is 'A ____ to learning English.'", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "\"We hope to preserve the historic value of these buildings and ____ serious parties to step", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A ____ card is an essential component of a games computer.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Remember that more than one ____ may be the cause of a problem and that symptoms may often overlap in their appearance.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ family is expected to drive past the school tomorrow morning. The children will be standing by the road waving flags.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some teachers believe that it is better to teach language to a class with students of ____ ability.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some subjects in our school have a higher ____ than others. Everyone wants to take science, but few want to study a second language.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child except one was more than ____ to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance ____ is independent of maternal ____, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest ____ between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Though all of them are presented in English, there is a significant ____ in clarity between the various reports.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Such activity cannot be considered an ____ substitute for excellence in teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When he left home he planned to ____ from Christianity to Buddhism, but then he decided he didn't believe in any god.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The police are looking for a woman of ____ height, last seen wearing a red jacket.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The committee was asked to ____ a report listing the reasons in favour of invading Iraq.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It offers an ____ solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills minor as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief ____ for lunch, he stared at the history project which was due the next morning.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ____ answer.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We will ____ to see new immigrants coming to our city, and we will need to guarantee their access into the medical care system.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although we did train the faculty in the revised teaching methods, in hindsight our training was not ____ enough to prepare them for the new course.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has failed in its primary task, ____ to reduce unemployment.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This survey examines attitudes ____ the campus-area housing market.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The book is at its best when it delves energetically into some particular event, and draws out its ____ meaning with reference to the grand themes.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What is the next letter in the ____ O, T, F, S, N, E, _?", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to help each other, but is spite also part of the human condition?", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "DeRosa's success is a genuine example of how the right ____ and excellent faculty really can cause a scholarly transformation.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The fat cells that surround coronary arteries may play a central and previously unrecognized ____ in the development of cardiovascular disease.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Candidates must demonstrate a high ____ of responsibility, the ability to work independently, and a strong commitment to customer service.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was also no ____ record of an attempt to measure the relationship between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In all such cases, we are happy to refund the ____ price and shipping charges once the prints are returned to us, at your expense, in good condition.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some subjects in our school have a higher ____ than others. Everyone wants to take science, but few want to study a second language.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "status", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "position, standing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Recent research shows ____ against African American mothers of any class who don't work.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Because of the shortage of wheat, ____ to persistent wet weather, the price of bread has risen in the last few weeks.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally rigid bodies undergo multiple, concurrent, ____ frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It only drew more ____ to the 13-year-old Robertson panel report and the CIA's role in the investigation of UFOs.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government made the prompt decision to kill all cows in the ____ before the disease could spread.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Wilhelm Wundt began writing on psychology and psychophysics as early as 1858, even though he did not ____ his laboratory until 1879.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must devise a plan to remove greenhouse gases from the ____ without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This book provides the definitive ____ of the origins of coffee drinking.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "China is able to ____ goods cheaply because labour costs are low.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The students began to ____ when their teacher told them they would have a test on the last day before Christmas.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Curiously absent from the report is any ____ of the type of action that the State would have taken against the diverse sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The student said that his dog had eaten his homework. The teacher did not believe him but could not ____ what he said.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has banned smoking in ____ all public places.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This ____ ignorance was caused by the insufficient amount of media coverage on topic.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an annual security report detailing statistics ____ crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This section of the GED web site provides ____ example questions from each part of the GED Tests.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The priests of this institution did not give their answers by inspiration, but occupied themselves chiefly with the ____ of dreams", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The tax system must not discourage economic activity and it must not ____ from the tax systems in other countries.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This also helps you ____ which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ambiguous answer.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many undergraduates have little ____ in organizing tasks and making good use of time.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is often necessary to revise a mathematical model several times in the course of an ____ operations research study.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "By signing the pledge, students make a personal commitment to conserve energy and help ____ to Yale's goal of reducing greenhouse gases by 10 percent.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on behalf of another, the ____ steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "His idea is simply not ____ - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The data is ambiguous as some analysts measure this ____ according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "China won't take strong action ____ Iran's nuclear program because China just made a deal to buy lots of Iranian oil.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It circles the theater so that you can ____ projectors at any spot on the dome, whereas before we were limited to placing them toward the back of the room.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is research that could ____ help in the treatment of certain kinds of cancer.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A headache may seem like a ____ problem, but it could be the sign of something more serious.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the impulse to improve his ____ poor grades.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My initial ____ was to resign, but then I changed my mind.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Eat less, exercise more: the ____ for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The eagle is ____ of carrying animals nearly as heavy as itself a great distance.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many talented local young people have had to ____ graduate or professional education because of lack of access to such programs.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Dr. Glick is an ____ in community and public health nursing programs and issues.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "So, the possibility of humans bringing about ____ evil is a logical consequence of having free will.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The new rules will ____ to anyone who has come to Germany in the last 10 years.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Your supervisor has been provided with the above information and should be able to ____ any questions you may have.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The European Union attempts to align ____ and financial practices in its member countries.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government needs to find a better device for restricting the ____ amounts of money earned by top directors.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This ____ in your writing doesn't make sense. What are you trying to say?", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more on the books that you read. It's not enough to just write what happens.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They ____ their nutrients from the air and not from the plant on which they are growing.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design phase will ____ that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Teachers can suggest that students get a minimum of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot ____ it.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This finding may explain why increasing numbers of people in the United States lack the natural ____ to regulate food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most leadership training programs leave out the key question, namely how leaders actually ____ their groups.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Despite the political, ____ and cultural success of the Arab city states, Islam for many years did not spread into the interior of East.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more ____ against unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to ____ the political support needed to maintain funding for the integrated service program.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This ____ text contains the typical method of trisecting a segment.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In tomorrow's TV broadcast the government will ____ its intention to reduce taxes during its time in office.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This review found that some guidelines and standards for reprocessing ____ laryngoscopes are incomplete, inadequate, and not consistent with one another.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Health Minister has made the ____ request that parents make sure their children eat enough fruit and vegetables.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In most countries the ____ for the place where you can get information is the letter 'i'.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "His current measurement results are not precise enough to identify exactly the ____ that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you are accepted you will need to ____ to have an official copy of your scores sent to the Program address below.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I can survive on a ____ income. I don't need lots of money.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Why are most intellectuals and education theorists so hostile to allowing ____ parents to choose which school their children will attend?", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "By running these ads, the newspaper is sending the message that it considers this a ____ product to sell.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "How can the traditional classroom and the technology in it ____ deeper learning?", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is not an infinite ____ of oil and natural gas.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Ambition was not an ____ of the female characters in his earlier films.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For this task, instructors present a ____ of steps in a mixed order and students are asked to re-order the items into the correct sequence.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The project itself may grow out of course work, but it must ____ achievement that is over and above regular course activities.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Forests are both an important part of the global ecosystem and an important ____ of raw materials for lumber, paper, and fuelwood.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Despite the enormous amount of ____ invested in her language teaching she was not able to construct grammatical sentences.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You ____ yourself to unnecessary danger if you drive a car without wearing a seat belt.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Injuries occur when there is a certain blow or pressure against the head, damaging the ____ of the brain.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "At the end of the lesson please put the ____ back in the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If he is correct this would certainly be an ____ solution to an ancient problem.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Another reason to monitor student e-mail and internet usage is to ____ their safety.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The CLAS Institute identifies, evaluates, and promotes effective and appropriate early intervention and preschool practices that are sensitive to ____ cultural and linguistic backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Could you please restore this book to its ____ place on the shelf.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Government scientists have ____ some red areas on the surface of Jupiter, but they do not know yet what these signify.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam depend very heavily on ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Hopkins argues that the district court committed three ____ errors in determining his sentence.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Perhaps the most elaborate example of an arthropod joint, ____ one of the most complex skeletal structures known, is the wing hinge of insects.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The referee of a football match can ____ the offside flag of his or her linesman.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a fund to give someone the opportunity to ____ higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Flights from Athens to the island are on small planes which fill up quickly; they are not very ____ and are often booked several months in advance.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The water cycle is one of the natural processes that are ____ to most students.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Government ministers should not ____ on matters outside of their own domain; they often do not know enough about such topics.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He uses Blanche White to ____ the problems of color and class difference between blacks and whites.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "His problems are ____ due to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The last week of the tennis tournament will ____ the first week of the Olympic Games.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The police are looking for a woman of ____ height, last seen wearing a red jacket.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When morality comes up against ____, it is seldom ____ that loses.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many stores have special offers to ____ new customers.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The most important ____ of the new design is that it consumes less power.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a widespread belief ____ the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is no coincidence that the early proponents of so-called ____ education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and worth of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In this article I will discuss the possible use of ____ speech recognition (ASR) for training students to improve their accents in a foreign language.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "preliminary", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "first; initial", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We are going to ____ this photograph to poster size and put it on the classroom wall.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The angry shouts from demonstrators at the back of the hall did not ____ the politician in his speech.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She wanted to ____ and to reorganize the departmental program but was not able to convince the school administration.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The sports hall is on the school grounds but it doesn't ____ to the school.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Our focus is to ____ each student to achieve their full potential as they strive for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Is anyone in class ____ with the terms 'subject' and 'predicate'?", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For most teachers the cash bonus was a nice acknowledgment of work well done, but not an ____ that influenced their behavior.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The mask must always ____ the actor in expressing both joy and grief.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no trace of an ____ idea in this essay.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "On the back of this form or on a separate sheet, write a ____ statement describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her ____ efforts throughout the school year are certain to yield excellent results in her final examinations.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We ____ all our efforts and resources to the education and preparation of all students.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The numbers of overweight and obese children worldwide are expected to climb ____ by 2010.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The United States is a nation pulling ____ to a degree unknown in the last 25 years.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "After massive criticism the government has decided to ____ language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We will not ____ the personal property of co-workers and customers, and will respect their right to privacy.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "What steps do I take to draw a random sample of a ____ audience in my county to do a needs assessment or gather baseline data?", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Oil is becoming more and more scarce. It is ____ that we find new ways of powering cars and industry.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Our very ____ makes us aware of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His idea is simply not ____ - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A major ____ in the proposal is that there is not sufficient money to finance it.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The precise answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is related in a particular way to the ____ of time.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She has gained ____ good grades since she has started attending school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Due to its association with the churches and schools, the Samoan language enjoyed high ____ in Tokelau for a long time.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was perhaps the most significant ____ of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Farmers in Germany complain every summer about the ____ of people who are prepared to work in the fields harvesting asparagus or strawberries.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I'm trying to ____ a machine that will do my homework for me. - Good luck!", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is no ____ upon her behaviour at home. She is allowed to do whatever she wants.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The grant is not a sufficient ____ for the excellence and hard work of this faculty and staff.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Developed countries should ____ some of their wealth with poorer nations in Africa.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids transmit ____ better than air.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The police found it difficult to ____ the two groups of opposing demonstrators.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "People with mental disabilities are so marginalized that even human rights activists have failed to ____ for them.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you accept a housing assignment in the Summer Allocation and subsequently ____ it or fail to move in, you are charged an administrative fee.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Through much of the War, the U.S. and its Allies could not ____ a fully effective blockade against Germany.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Do not ____ all your energy in the first 20 minutes. Remember that the game lasts for half an hour!", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The prime minister has said that he has no plan to resign over the ____ in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ a lot of money in a new arts and technology block.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "At the end of the lesson please put the ____ back in the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Every year in Germany many people lose all their ____ when their houses burn down in a fire.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government reduced its ____ to the Arts Council after it was found that much of the money had been wasted.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will ____ your chances of success if you are absent from school so often.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I went on a long ____ last year. First I travelled to Japan, then I flew to Brazil. After that I sailed to California before coming home.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We do not ____ a unilateral ban on cosmetic testing on animals, nor do we reject the use of animals in biomedical research.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Not any of these persons shall perform or ____ any practice that may damage the reputation of the university.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For many persons these are not trivial concerns but ____ and deep beliefs.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Through the exhibit and its constant updating, people will be able to ____ new, thought- provoking works of art from around the globe.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Generic skills cannot be considered as ____ of subject matter. Moreover, a good part of teaching involves thinking, problem- solving, and decision making.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "average", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "ordinary, typical"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school does a lot to ____ new families, with information meetings, translation services, etc.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Prices have risen by ____ 4% over the last 10 years.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This year you cannot choose which science course to do, but when you are in grade 9 you can ____ chemistry, physics or biology.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If the picture on your TV is not very clear, you need to ____ the controls.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school is looking for students who would like to do ____ work at the local old people's home.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is no point having a law if the police are not ____ to enforce it.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They are never forgotten, those ____ moments of splendid victory sandwiched between so many slices of rancid defeat.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ issue is, and always has been, one of parenting.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The current ____ of our anatomy information system has evolved from several previous systems.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "form"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When two atoms of hydrogen ____ with one of oxygen, then the result is H2O, water.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you are a ____ of the school orchestra should have lunch early and come to the practice at 12.30.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that ____ and globalization also threaten to accelerate environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The last ____ of the flooded village was evacuated by a helicopter.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "controversy", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When you finish unit 1, please do the questions and then ____ to unit 3. You don't need to do unit 2.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Let us hope that the new government does not ____ the mistakes of the previous one.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and ____ invisible to ships.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting threaten to raise water levels and ____ flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "To achieve this goal, planning must ____ the best available scientific information and analysis.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The angry shouts from demonstrators at the back of the hall did not ____ the politician in his speech.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She is being ____ concerned about the exams. She will certainly pass.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You may need to ____ to the terms and scope of the permission (i.e., duration, purpose, etc.).", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our very ____ makes us aware of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Her consistent efforts throughout the school year are certain to ____ excellent results in her final examinations.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you ____ the stairs by the nurse's office, you will see the cafeteria in front of you.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Religion is an ____ in which many people have very strong feelings.", "Opt_1": "formula", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The minister gave an ____ answer when asked if the government intended to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some people advocate government elections every four years ____ of every five as at present.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Roman Catholic Church along with the main Protestant denominations in Europe did not ____ the slave trade.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Close to 30% of students did not ____ it to be cheating to lie to an instructor about having an illness or some other emergency in order to extend a work deadline.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has announced its ____ for the introduction of the new tax system over the next 5 years.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There are ____ areas under the sea that have not yet been explored.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has set up a ____ to assist refugees on entry to the country.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Despite the enormous amount of ____ invested in her language teaching she was not able to construct grammatical sentences.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These ever-changing factors necessitate the creation of a flexible ____ that can respond and adapt to the needs of our library users.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This emphasis on improving student outcomes will persist in the immediate future as the dominant factor in determining the success or failure of education ____ strategies.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we cover less familiar territory, ____ the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We have a rigid ____ of no drugs in our school. You will be expelled if you are caught with them in the building.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He mentioned what seemed like a huge sum. It was ____ a huge amount for a programme that had only a skeleton staff and strained budget.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "so"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While we are less concerned with the politics of Nigeria, we understand that a stable ____ situation would be to our advantage.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The search results are ____ to include lots of hits that are not particularly relevant to your topic.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "satisfactory", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a reasonable request for extension of the project ____ date.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have ____ to your medical record, thus is unable to obtain insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The rise in the price of oil is set to ____ in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I have no ____ to students wearing hats in the classroom, but many teachers do.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is suitable for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For some older people the ____ to new technologies has not been very smooth.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Her consistent efforts throughout the school year are certain to yield excellent results in her ____ examinations.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The dropout ____ for high schoolers rose to 3.8 percent during the last decade.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The main ____ of her poor grades are her frequent absences from school.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The test will be a ____ of reading comprehension passages and short writing texts.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is no magic ____ for getting better in English, but lots of reading is an easy and enjoyable way to improve.", "Opt_1": "formula", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teachers must accompany students and ____ activities in the computer room.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Thanks to the accurate ____ of the witnesses, the police were able to identify the bank robbers.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was bold of him to ____ the boss in front of all the workers.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She was quickly able to ____ the difficulty of speaking little English, and now she is easily the best student in the class.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has decided to revise it proposals to increase ____ tax after massive demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "An employee or University student who wishes the matter to receive a formal investigation and ____ should contact the EEO Officer.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Attendance will not ____ a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will definitely fail this course.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "constitute", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is overspending and will soon ____ all the money set aside for books and other materials.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "depend", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will ____ an email from the Financial Aid office when your financial aid eligibility has been determined.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The 9-11 Commission failed to mention or ____ the multiple war game exercises that were being conducted that day, out of the White House.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For my next step I would propose to the students certain distinctions that might at first glance seem to be completely ____ or valueless.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Weight loss is a constant ____ for many Americans.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Having access to the laptop does seem to have substantially increased the overall feeling of having ____ resources to do the job.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is very little ____ of the poor and middle class as our corrupt judges have developed a system called lawyer denial.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is an important finding that has implications for the ____ and treatment of children with PTSD.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is an advantage for a politician to be able to give a clear but concise ____ of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The conclusion did not distort the ____ of the situation even though the student distorted some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Close to 30% of students did not perceive it to be cheating to lie to an instructor about having an illness or some other emergency in ____ to extend a work deadline.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "role", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "job or function", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The expulsion of a student for smoking in the toilets caused a big ____ in the school.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The student was reported to the headmaster for continually trying to ____ the class.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Never has the ____ of a stable, prosperous, and democratic hemisphere seemed so close within reach.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that ____ and globalization also threaten to accelerate environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first ____ those principles and then consider the subsequent problems.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase level of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to ____ its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the item did not ____ the positive developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After the attacks of September 11, 2001, Pat Cornell turned her ____ to detecting and preventing terrorism.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Individuals should report the incident to a faculty or staff ____ at the university with whom they are comfortable.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is important to ____ possible solutions that hunters and ranchers feel have no potential to resolve conflicts.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A student enrolled in these types of courses really didn't get to know the instructor well and ____ did not feel any sense of community.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Your target heart ____ is a useful way of pacing yourself during exercise.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many new astronomy learners, students and adults alike, are unfamiliar with the universe ____ the solar system.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The journey to peace and prosperity in the region can only ____ when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Rumours about teachers ____ quickly through schools.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not always possible to distinguish a cause of a conflict from a ____ of that conflict.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is to the government's credit that they refused to ____ in the invasion of Iraq.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more ____ against unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "hostile", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The students had to ____ the planned class picnic when the day started with heavy rain and wind.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The board was unable to ____ a candidate in the first round because of disagreement over candidates' performance.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and ____ of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government ____ a warning about the dangers of terrorist attack in the capital city.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I think the students enjoy the fact that they have the ____ to try different things, says Harris. You can ask them to expand and see which direction they take.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government's election defeat is a ____ case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "FAQ > How do I ____ for free health services?", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "But when planned and ____ policy forces the price of oil down without good commercial reasons, then that means another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In history lessons we learn about many ____ peoples such as the Egyptians who built the pyramids, and Roman emperors like Julius Caesar.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it feasible to ____ someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I have set myself the ____ of learning all these 1000 academic words by the end of the school year. That's 8 per day!", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Children ____ in classes where their teachers care about each of them as individuals.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our programme provides professional development in the ____ of DNA sequencing and genomics for graduates.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Individual academies apply the curriculum in the ____ that best fits local facilities and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Dr. Blumenthal begins by analyzing why health care reform ____ failed to pass Congress in 1994.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The PBL method is rather time-consuming and requires the teacher to ____ a lot of effort over an extended period of time.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Nevertheless, thirty-three years later, Israel is not willing to ____ from the Golan Heights to the 4 June 1967, prewar border.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Under the new plan, the garden would remain at its current ____ on Walnut and Virginia streets and the pumping station would be built on the northeast.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The US, which by this time was paying most of France's war expenses, was unable to ____ the French to fight on.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Prime Minister broke off her visit to China ____ to an urgent problem at home.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You have not yet mastered ____ grammar. You still make mistakes like \"he go\" or she don't\".", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Advances in technology have increased the ____ of life and the ____ of change.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her ____ absence from school is the principal reason for her bad grades in the final exams.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Community service has helped me to ____ the contradictions that we live in.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If faculty ____ that a mental health problem may be the cause of a student's violation of the Student Code of Conduct, they should contact the Dean of Students immediately.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The German army planned to advance as far as Moscow, but were then stopped by the ____ Russian winter.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's good to see students of different nationalities interact so ____ as they do at our school.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "____ments cannot govern without the broad assent of the people.", "Opt_1": "Connect", "Opt_2": "Develop", "Opt_3": "Govern", "Opt_4": "Denote", "Answer": "Govern", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When does the unborn baby become an ____ separate from its mother?", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "People who suffer from hay fever cannot have real flowers in their house. They have ____ ones instead.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge ____ regarding the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Unlike other animals, humans have no ____ for survival; we often choose to do things that may be detrimental to our health.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most people have a ____ notion of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most simply, the strength of a ____ is measured by determining how much energy is required to break the ____.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Newton's Laws provide a good ____ of the flight of a baseball.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "They have made a ____ error in the way they are thinking about the opportunities and problems their business face.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is not the government's ____ to tell its citizens how to live.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "role", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "job or function", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The main consequence of these wars is the social unrest, and the increasing ____ and social divergence between the groups of the community.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "forthcoming", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "coming soon", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The cost of establishing links will ____ as improvements are made to the underlying communication infrastructure.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The spaceship has been sending back ____ images of Jupiter as it flies past on its way to the edge of the solar system.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I'm sorry but the school has no ____ to educate children with severe learning problems.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The teacher made the ____ decision to take her class out to the playground and finish the lesson there.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The reporter is interested in the ____ of elementary school teachers who have at least 20 years of experience.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "proportion", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is often necessary to revise a mathematical model several times in the course of an ____ operations research study.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "No program has developed an approach that is ____ successful in working with the types of problems that we try to solve.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ put forward in this paper depends in no degree upon the completeness of our knowledge of the former condition of the organic world.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore apart a nation and created many social problems that did not ____ before its invention.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If the number of sections to be taught does not ____ to the number of students, you need to explain the reason.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Before the ____ on smoking in public places there was usually a dense cloud of smoke at the end of the evening in bars and restaurants.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "form", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must devise a plan to ____ greenhouse gases from the atmosphere without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Future research would need to ensure that participants did not ____ in any other activities immediately prior to the study at hand.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Individuals should report the ____ to a faculty or staff member at the university with whom they are comfortable.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ to be recognized, to be considered important is not superficial. It is a basic human drive.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ its reluctance to advising parents how to bring up their children.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Because of the increase in the price of oil the company was unable to ____ to its plans to employ new workers.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is principally because they ____ the church and family as sources of emotional support.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Not everyone knows that Texas was once a ____ of Mexico.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you ____ the data further, you will see that there are many observations that are larger than 600.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is the duty of educators to ____ themselves carefully for each and every lesson.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My ____ to work every day takes me past my old school.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To ____ this from happening, it is very helpful for patients to avoid talking unless absolutely necessary for three days following surgery.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The tax system must not discourage economic activity and it must not ____ from the tax systems in other countries.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The fact that she doesn't speak English did much to ____ the situation.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The management wanted to ____ the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to replace him.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We recognize that ____ beyond a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The village system made it almost impossible to ____ the amount of land available for pasture.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Even the older ____ does have some command of the Indonesian language.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I prefer to believe that the quality of my thinking has not diminished; I simply have chosen a different ____ to express my ideas.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To what ____ do you believe that the government has made the right decision?", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its various Auxiliaries, shall meet a minimum ____ for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The conclusion did not distort the ____ of the situation even though the student distorted some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Pick a global issue and collect a ____ of newspaper articles and/or news clips on it during the semester.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When you finish unit 1, please do the questions and then ____ to unit 3. You don't need to do unit 2.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is very little ____ of the poor and middle class as our corrupt judges have developed a system called lawyer denial.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ancient puzzle involving three pegs, and an ____ number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will need to get your parents' ____ for your attendance at the sex education classes.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The third ____ of the writing process is when you revise your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its structure or content.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I asked for a concise ____ of what happened. So why have you given me a 20-page report?", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design ____ will assure that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam depend very heavily on ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The medical company decided to ____ production of its heart drug when it heard reports of the unexplained deaths of many people who had been taking it.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After much debate the school has decided to ____ students with physical disabilities.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Plants that possess certain traits or characteristics not common to the ____ species are referred to as biotypes.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Prime Minister broke off her visit to China due to an ____ problem at home.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You need to ____ your ideas a little better. It's difficult to follow what you are trying to say.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Your English is ____ improving, but you'll have to make greater effort if you want to get better more quickly.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of the government's willingness to pay kidnappers to release hostages is that now there are more kidnappings and more hostages.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "vary", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He mentioned what seemed like a huge sum. It was ____ a huge amount for a programme that had only a skeleton staff and strained budget.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The company yesterday said it made a ____ of \ufffd\ufffd217.46 million for the six months to June.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is very ____ for a student to learn English so quickly. But she has!", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "rare", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Research into heart disease has revealed a clear pattern: those who smoke too much, drink too much and do not ____ enough are the most likely to suffer from it.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Its plot centers on how the ____ between two female \"mates\" is almost broken because both love the same man.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people think that the government ____ to reduce teenage pregnancy will not be successful.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "On your first day in a new school it is difficult to ____ all the information that you are given.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Why, Graeme Newman asks, has reform after reform failed to ____ the spread of crime?", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When they did investigations after 9-11, one of the major things that they came up with was that the various government agencies did not ____ the dots.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to gather the political support needed to ____ funding for the integrated service program.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Further analysis suggested that the ____ was worse for women than men.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Any student who is at least 13 years old on September 30 is ____ to enter the mathematics competition.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I need to speak to John's parents ____ his constant absence.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Typical conversations ____ a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans accumulate as they grow.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs include walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs ____ of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Lebanese security officials said the soldiers' tank drove over a mine, but Israel said it could not ____ that.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An abundance of research documents the biased and harsh ____ that Black defendants have received at the hands of predominantly White jurors.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Studies show that parents ____ influence the development of their child in all areas.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most of Africa suffers to some ____ from similar issues: weak institutions, stagnant economies, ethnic conflict, etc.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Our focus is to motivate each student to achieve their full potential as they ____ for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Future research would need to ensure that participants did not ____ in any other activities immediately prior to the study at hand.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to encourage the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and ____ employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam depend very heavily on ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government's election ____ is a classic case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Web sites such as Wikipedia certainly ____ the finding of information, although not all of it is reliable.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The wishes of parents must not always override the recommendations of the teachers about the ____ choices of the child.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Despite all the money spend on cancer research there is little ____ of a cure being found in the near future.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ the school day until 4:30.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The cost of transporting diesel fuel to operate machines in the arctic ____ is very high, typically 2-4 times world market prices.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to ____ profound changes in society.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ area of Frankfurt is to the south east of the city center.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Each student's ____ was so varied that I was unable to isolate common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students are strongly recommended to seek assistance from the Student Rights Officer at their campus should they decide to appeal ____ exclusion.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Van Haarlem also said the team had found a large ____ of what may have been a ceramic baboon statue.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He is the inevitable ____ for the leading role in the play. He's by far the best actor in the school.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Iowa State Theater group will ____ \"The Complete Works of William Shakespeare\" five times during the festival.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "California's medical schools and major teaching hospitals are directly and ____ responsible for more than 200000 full-time jobs.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "To ____ white light into its component colors with a prism and use an identical prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of the new science building is not finished yet, but from the outside it looks great!", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was not a ____ that anybody in the world would consider wise.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The result of the school's drive to ____ student eating habits is that far fewer plates of French fries are now sold in the cafeteria.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I ____ the idea of having a school uniform. I think it would cause a lot of unnecessary problems.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There will be ____ of time for questions after each speaker finishes their presentation.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Customers found no ____ in comparison -shopping, since price uniformity was nearly absolute.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Do not ____ the period after an abbreviation such as in. (for inch), which could be confused with the word in.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While you may not admit to ____ pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Why did the Bush Administration refuse to ____ its goals in order to achieve a consensus?", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The festival was a ____ disaster: there was no food, no medical assistance, the rain and overpopulation made the place a living hell.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Wikipedia is a wonderful ____ for high school students, but the information it contains must be checked for reliability.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Student surveys find teaching to be too uniformly didactic, and their learning too passive. Students report spending ____ class time just taking notes.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government looks ____ to succeed in its objective to reduce child poverty by the end of the decade.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Please ____ the Timetable for class times and locations.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ocean floor is the last great ____ waiting to be exploited for its oil and other minerals.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There has been no ____ statement about the number of soldiers who were killed in the fighting.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As large and difficult as it was, it was not the ____ problem. The deeper problem was conceptual.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The failures of the national soccer and tennis teams ____ all that is wrong with British sport.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company directors made a ____ attempt to save the business by dismissing half the workforce.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "preliminary", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "first; initial", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some scientists believe that there is an ____ supply of oil waiting to be discovered at the bottom of deep oceans.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Contrary to what you've been told by Courtney Love and the manipulated media reports, Kurt Cobain had no ____ for suicide.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Asia is our closest ____ and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and exchange culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar symbol of ____ to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They argued that the law did not ____ to Cheney's task force, since all of its members were government officials, not outsiders.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company has decided to devote its main ____ to increasing business in the developing Chinese market.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He is an American citizen which obviously puts him in a different ____ from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She was very feminine, yet very strong, very ____ under the surface.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Based on the results, they will have to ____ the tests as often as once every three months or as rarely as once every five years.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Example: She doesn't have a very good ____ with her parents.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She is yet to ____ basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I thoroughly ____ this book to anybody interest in the vegetation of North America and to those studying similar vegetation in other parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Since that time two ____ surveys were conducted with an attempt to define the scope of the problem.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Part of the job of an ESL teacher in an international school is to ____ the need to make work comprehensible to non-native speakers.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Working with the Teacher Assistant is not ____ but recommended.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ is not a sufficient reward for the excellence and hard work of this faculty and staff.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a very clear ____ in the school for expelling students who do not follow the rules.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She would have a better chance of academic success if she didn't ____ in so many activities outside of school.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an appropriate ____ to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Under these treaties, US warships did not have to ____ the nature of the weapons they carried.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The company's ____ plan was to close down only one of their factories. Because of continuing bad sales, however, they were forced to close three of them.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These three young women have exhibited the kind of inner strength, commitment to friendship, patience and self-control that one ____ sees.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to ____ the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and retain employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A color model is an orderly system for creating a whole ____ of colors from a small set of primary colors.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His problems at school started to ____ when he began spending hours on the internet every evening.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "arise", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If your parents want too take you out of school during term time, they must have a ____ reason.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Traditional social skills strategies (such as board games about friendships and appropriate classroom behavior) ____ to be too subtle for many children.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The controversy resulted from the fact that the Jews agreed to the resolution but the local Arabs refused to ____ the Israeli State.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not ____ ourselves and therefore our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may ____ an inaccurate or superficial analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The profession of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and ____ of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We are heading for a ____ in our health system. Not enough people want to be doctors.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Governments are considering how to exploit the ____ mineral resources buried under the ice in Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Nature was an ____ part of ancient Chinese, Japanese, and Indian literature.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most important ____ to her learning is that she never does her homework.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many people buy ____ vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their regular food.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between learning your first language and learning a second one.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "forthcoming", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "coming soon", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If the funding is from personal or family funds, you will need to ____ a current bank statement showing that you have enough funds to cover expenses.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to ____ from power cycle failure, but this is not a concern for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "suffer", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I think the students enjoy the fact that they have the ____ to try different things, says Harris. You can ask them to expand and see which direction they take.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school needs to ____ the students' project work to the examination board before the end of the month.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Scientists are hoping that it may soon be possible to ____ the weather.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In order to make up a missed exam, you must ____ written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a legitimate reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There was not the ____ of going to school; it was expected that you'd go to work and contribute to the family.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on behalf of another, the ____ steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Delivery of safe and timely care is a huge ____ given the complexities of modern medicine.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You will not have to seek permission to publish if the ____ of your work falls under one of the following criteria.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A ____ of nature is the way a stick seems to break when it is looked at under water.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has given \ufffd\ufffd10 million to fight AidS in Africa, but some people believe that this ____ is not sufficient.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ancient puzzle involving three pegs, and an ____ number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Her problems are close to the surface and ____ to be expressed in more direct, less symbolic, behavioral and emotional terms.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government's ____ is that the bomb was set off by a recent immigrant.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Use this form when you need to ____ accidentally deleted files from the network.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As a musician it is not ____ to have skill. You must practise, practise, practise.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I want to ____ my ESL grade, so I'm going to try to read many more books next semester.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is well-known that knowledge of formal grammar rules does always not ____ with the ability to teach the language.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The B grade had come to signify work that was ____ acceptable.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has only had ____ success in reducing the number of unemployed people.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "So, what's the ____ of all this hindsight and what do we stand to gain from it?", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is beyond the ____ of this course.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I don't really like science but my parents decided to ____ me to take biology and chemistry in grade 10.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "compel", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It must have been about this time that Stalin took the most extraordinary decision of his career in order to ____ his political survival.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The prime minister has decided to cancel the planned visit to Batavia in ____ of the outbreak of war in the country.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many people ____ before eating raw fish for the first time. They are not sure what it will taste like.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The course introduces students to the structure and function of cities and ways planners solve ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He flew in with 500 rolls of film and 1400 pounds of provisions but forgot to ____ for the pilot to pick him up again.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Could you please ____ this book to its proper place on the shelf.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ farmers who grow crops that can be used to run cars.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government was ____ successful in reducing teenage drinking during its first period in power.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In infants without a family history of food allergies, there is no need to restrict or ____ any specific foods.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Venus will next ____ in the night sky in August 2007.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief interval for lunch, he stared at the history project which was ____ the next morning.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most basic ____ to develop is observational drawing skills.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many British citizens and their political and ____ leaders were suspicious of Napoleon's motives and would not cooperate, so the tunnel project was abandoned.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students are responsible for gathering all materials necessary to ____ an appeal.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A Parisian mob broke into the palace killing many of the guards, while searching for the ____ family.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Repeat this procedure until only a small amount of ____ is released when it is vented.", "Opt_1": "assignment", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They met resistance from Nigerian government officials who did not welcome change and did not want to hear the ____ about the AidS epidemic in Nigeria.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All of his projects ____ the idea of flexibility within different, changing environments.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The shortening of the lunch break caused ____ between the workers and the management.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The rising price of oil could result in a global ____ disaster.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They ____ their nutrients from the air and not from the plant on which they are growing.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government clearly did not ____ carefully enough on the consequences of its new law.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "FLO plays the key role as an ____ for ethically sensitive consumers.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How can the traditional classroom and the technology in it ____ deeper learning?", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government said that it had no ____ to give the reasons for its decision.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The American colonists did not ____ a real newspaper of their own for another century.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is a widespread belief that scaling up HIV ____ counseling and testing (VCT) programs in Africa will have large prevention benefits.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is just a ____ to get your attention.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A student enrolled in these types of courses really didn't get to know the instructor well and ____ did not feel any sense of community.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As a simple soldier he gained much credit by conducting a retreat after all the ____ officers had been killed or wounded.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "superior", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We all have to tolerate differences of opinion in the ____ world and, in order to do that, we have to understand that there are real reasons for these differences.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We have found that students are more likely to complete a ____ health project if they join a team.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In future we will increasingly need to ____ wind and sun power as fossil fuels such as coal and oil become more expensive.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was little ____ that the government's plans to increase taxes would be very unpopular.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The last death occurred on Thursday morning when a deaf man apparently walking to work did not ____ a police order to halt and was shot.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Sitting too long in front of a computer may ____ headaches or back problems.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teachers often ____ student grammar errors with a yellow marker pen.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This ____ can be applied to various educational and medical issues.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has made ____ any progress towards reducing environmental pollution.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was a ____ demonstration on the streets of London to protest the government's plans to go to war in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government met this morning to ____ how to help people who have been hit by the flood crisis.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was difficult for the two sides in the dispute to find a ____ time to meet.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A major problem for most western societies is how to ____ immigrants with different cultures and religious beliefs.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students are able to use basic communication and mathematics skills for purposes and situations they will ____ throughout their lives.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They felt this was an unreliable ____ due to poor data and that the harvest could in fact increase.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is not a defect in the notion of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal ____ of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The case of Nicaragua demonstrates how the United States failed to ____ on the implementation of democratic procedures.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Government ministers laid flowers at the ____ of the terrorist explosion.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The decision to make cannabis legal in small amounts is a significant ____ in the government's policy.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This forecast showed much less ____ than expected by the district's officials and residents.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "On the back of this ____ or on a separate sheet, write a thorough statement describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people claim that the ____ of the internet has been to the detriment of students' ability and willingness to read.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "order", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The campus will be closed ____ for needed emergency services and essential work.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are ____ laws that govern the trade in rainforest wood.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Increased ____ caused consumers to spend more and firms to invest more.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In a densely populated area, an earthquake may do far more ____ than one of greater magnitude that occurs in a remote area.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The prime minister has said that he has no plan to ____ over the crisis in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The latest problems to ____ with the red maple tree are a result of the extreme weather patterns and environmental stress.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "arise", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We can only ____ that Fulton was already too deeply committed to his own plan to consider alternative ideas.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The prompt response of the Hu Jintao government has won ____ praise, both inside and outside China.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Her efforts have continued to ____ in the last few months. I think she may be having problems at home.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To set up a practice test, I'd ____ a zero point test with questions from the year before in random order with random answers.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A sound card is an essential ____ of a games computer.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was an ____ conservative institution, and did not enlarge its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The way that people are raised as children will usually ____ the way that they act as adults.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I regard what people actually do in practice as far more significant and worthy of formalization than what ivory-tower logicians ____ in principle.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this field of study will have abundant opportunities to ____ personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will be required to know the questions and issues that the various authors raise and the approaches they ____ in their research.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to make inferences and hold causal beliefs, even though it is not rational.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Our experiments with SRM 1010a led us to the conclusion that this was too ____ a method of evaluating results.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many arguments would not develop if people would ____ the words they use.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The plants in many of the world's ____ places have not yet been analysed for their possible medical effects.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you can't do your homework, you should ask your parents to ____ you.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For my next step I would ____ to the students certain distinctions that might at first glance seem to be completely arbitrary or valueless.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Do you think that the school will ____ the suggestion to increase the number of holidays?", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The student could not ____ the basic factors in a solution to the problem.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Volleyball players must ____ in order, and every player must do this (i.e. a team may NOT have a designated setter/hitter/etc. who does not ____ out).", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The information that you receive in today's lesson will ____ you to complete your project on nuclear energy.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Check with your academic advisor if you are uncertain whether this will count as a ____ towards your graduation.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to ____ with it.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You must remember to ____ all the images and other HTML documents you have created and referenced in your \"Public/html\" directory.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of the proposal is to deprive people of the liberty to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You'll save yourself a lot of work if you concentrate on creating a healthy lawn, ____ than the manicured look.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please ____ Einstein to your list of famous scientists.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She is yet to ____ basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This widespread ____ was caused by the insufficient amount of media coverage on topic.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of the students' time is spent performing experiments, with required one-on-one mentorship by a graduate student, fellow, or faculty member.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His ____ is that if we don't cut taxes, then unemployment will rise.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many buildings ____ during earthquakes and kill the people inside.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was a ____ at the end of Obama's speech that caused his audience to jump up and start clapping.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In proof of this, we may note that slavery did not ____ immediately on the reception of Christianity.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The first principle of this school is that all nationalities and cultures are equally important, even if some are more represented than others ____ the body of students.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will not get a prompt ____ to your email. He is very busy at the moment.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They further alleged that the removal of the soil would ____ the quality of the district's drinking water.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their ____ whether it is safe to accept a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You will receive a lengthy, very ____ email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe request did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ambassador seems to have failed in his duty to correctly ____ the government he serves.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of your ideas and organization is much more important than the quantity of words you write.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In decimal notation we ____ a negative number by writing a minus in front of a positive number.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To justify their high salary, top managers like to ____ to the increased risk that they will lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "People with mental disabilities are so marginalized that even human rights activists have failed to ____ for them.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students may take a longer time to complete this program, but a ____ of two semesters shall be devoted to full-time work and normally the program must be completed within eight calendar years.", "Opt_1": "concern", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The B grade had come to ____ work that was barely acceptable.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I'm not sure how to ____ any of these abstract terms, and yet I recognize some of the components of forgiveness.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The treatment must not risk ____ to any personal or public property.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government should ____ all its energy to reducing unemployment.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ____ answer.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The cakes ____ of flour, sugar, eggs and milk.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She had no ____ to practice architecture in the District.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A nursing or household robot must be ____ in order to reach a variety of working sites within the house.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We must ____ the trend of a growing incidence of campus hate crimes.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our very ____ makes us aware of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "How many planet/planet collisions do you ____ will come from the M31 incident - or do you think we will be smoothly assimilated?", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is usually a close ____ between students of the same nationality at an international school.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The most significant risk ____ in predicting whether a person will commit a violent crime in the future is whether the person has previous offenses.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Developments in computer technology may eventually make ____ weather forecasting possible.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I am ____ that you will do well in the examinations.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to ____ their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to join the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The European Union attempts to align ____ and financial practices in its member countries.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ its lunchtime sports program after hearing a request from the student council.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The method of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally ____ a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a comprehensive final exam.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There are ____ 350 students in high school. I'm not sure of the exact number.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Seminar is an intensive examination of ____ policy making in Washington.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Trying to water-ski for the first time is difficult but if you keep practising, you will ____ learn how to do it.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The proponents of disability rights and design professionals have come to realize that the ____ of accessible design has to be rethought.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was not wise to use the river as the ____ for your drinking water before you analyzed it.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ is the most common teaching style at university. There is not so much question and answer as in schools.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an annual security report detailing statistics ____ crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The court concluded that schools could not ____ disabled students whose disability causes their disruptive conduct.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The United Mine Workers was the recognized bargaining ____ for the coal miners in Illinois, Indiana, Ohio, and Pennsylvania.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Poor results in end of year tests often ____ that the teacher has not taught the course very well.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The university intend to make some changes in its admissions policy, but it cannot yet ____ what those changes will be.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Solving a problem of this ____ will require the collective will and shared sacrifice of all members of the university.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I am no expert in animal behavior, but anyone with even a ____ knowledge of the field must be impressed with their complex forms of social behavior.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If these reports are not returned, we will presume that you have used all ____ sick leave for that particular reporting period.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When you finish unit 1, please do the questions and then ____ to unit 3. You don't need to do unit 2.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The minister gave an ____ answer when asked if the government intended to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was not ____ to use the river as the source for your drinking water before you analyzed it.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The quality of your work has improved ____ in the last few weeks.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is an ____ pattern to her absences from school: Monday mornings and Friday afternoons!", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that ____ and globalization also threaten to accelerate environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your composition must ____ an introduction, a conclusion and three body paragraphs.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The USA is designing a spaceship that will land on Mars and ____ its polar regions.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In order to make up a missed exam, you must produce written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a ____ reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Standing on the table is certainly no way to ____ in the cafeteria!", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We must ____ the scientists and experts to make the right decisions to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its ____ Auxiliaries, shall meet a minimum standard for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In order to make student learning ____ to real life experiences, learning environments must be authentic.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a ____ implication on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}]]